"Imperial Ballad"
It sounds so good
The girl just made a wrong note
at the seventh place
This is the same
rather than picking
Sir, you really have a good ear
I actually heard this subtle difference
I wonder if you can play another song?
- Play one more - Play one more
One more song
Shopkeeper Yan
You can then be here
Listen to music and enjoy the moon
Shopkeeper Yan
This is like taking medicine
Gong Shangjiao Zhengyu
Harmony of five notes
Can heal the five internal organs
One song finished, illness retirement relief
Shopkeeper Yan will come next time
I would like to play the piano myself
Take you to experience this five-tone healing method
good…
Wait for the next opportunity
Definitely come and experience it yourself
Shopkeeper Yan
This is our Huiyinfang
Unique orange blossom fragrance
Helps sleep and calms the mind
You smell it
This is consistent with the scent of chess musicians
Then I want it even more
good
Shopkeeper Yan
This is Huiyinfang’s unique beauty cream
-This is unique to Huiyinfang... -Everything is required
As expected of Kyoto
There are so many things to pay attention to when listening to a piece of music
It really opened my eyes
Trouble, gentlemen
Send me to Bo Feng Building
yes
Mr. Xiao Shen is really a romantic person
Dandy and uninhibited
-Who is she? -Teaching girls to play dice in Shazhou
Drinking with ladies in Kyoto
Now I come to Huiyinfang to attract bees and butterflies.
Koshin adult Kashin is people watching love
The peach blossoms are endless
Shopkeeper Yan remembers it so clearly
Could it be that you care about me?
lecher
Shopkeeper Yan really turns his back faster than flipping through a book.
Just bought the restaurant yesterday
Today I turned against anyone and refused to recognize anyone.
I think shopkeeper Yan is also very lucky.
Hug left and right today
Show mercy everywhere
I came here to learn from the opening of Bo Feng Tower.
How does it look like you?
Wherever I go, I look like a butterfly.
Are you afraid that others won't know that you are a romantic person?
each other
I have something else to do today
Let’s talk about it another day
Business?
What can you do?
I checked Situ Xue’s household registration
She is from an ordinary person
After rising to prominence with Hua Chao Festival,
Buy Huiyinfang by performing music and performing arts
Since then, he has been operating his business
There are many dignitaries coming and going in Huiyinfang
Now the flowers of the past appear again
Is this a coincidence or another mystery? I don’t know yet.
And the crossbow arrows
It’s with Bei Jian
Is it still related to the original Zhongwan?
Don't break it lightly
You continue to stare at Huiyinfang
Get along well with Situ Xue
yes
The black bird is immortal
blood moon forever
Welcome Mr. Shangguan
Today Huionbo
Went as an uninvited guest
Sir, he really understands the overall situation
He came for Xiyanhua
This dog emperor found clues in Black Tiger Hall
Nowadays, Daning has very strict supervision over major military camps.
Our sources of ordnance
We have to find another way
I have ordered people to find a private mine
From now on
Send people to supervise work day and night
Forging weapons
in order to realize it as soon as possible
Restoration plan
But the British widows are already suspicious of us
Should we kill him first?
Take action rashly at this moment
It will definitely scare the snake away.
What I want is...
-Kill with one hit-Mr.
The subordinates also found out
Above the Daning court
The British oligarchs newly established the Procuratorate
It is intended to deprive the two prime ministers of their power.
And promote the new female champion Meng Tinghui
In charge of the Procuratorate
The court in Daning becomes more and more chaotic
The situation is more favorable to us
Find a way to get close to Meng Tinghui
It must be used by me
Subordinates take orders
Destroy Daning
Restoration of Zhongwan
adult
I've been prepared
Not afraid of ghosts
I'm not afraid of this thing
Protect Assistant Manager Shen
I'm not afraid either
Assistant Shen
I said you are a weak woman
You should stay at home
Mr. Meng can
Me too
Give it to you for free
Master Meng
This is it
That group of body thieves took over the mountain and became king
Digging up all the ancestral graves of the villagers
We need to spend money to redeem the bodies of our family members
Every year, we have to spend more than 100 taels to protect the body.
Only a place to be buried
A little bit of complaint
They will punch and kick us
After my grandfather's body was stolen
Grandma was overly sad and angry
He died too
How unreasonable
At the feet of the emperor
How could someone do such an unconscionable thing?
We applied for many times
The Ministry of Punishment ignored it at all
They also used various excuses to prevaricate us.
Said it was just a body lost
They are basically the same group
Where are those body thieves?
I have to meet you in person
They only show up when robbing corpses and extorting people.
Then wait until they throw themselves into a trap
Second Master
You are really clever
If I had known they would bury the body secretly
Sure enough, we found it
A bunch of useless things
This time we will charge them ten times the ransom, do you hear that?
My elder brother is just too kind.
Wait until I finish my work this time
I'll go ask the gang leader for credit
The gang leader will definitely let me take over the gang's business again.
you
Go and see if there are any new graves there
Yes, Second Master
Take it, don't move it
The Divine Guards are here
Who dares to make a mistake?
lay down
Hu Xiao Gang Lu Er
It’s been a long time
Lu Er?
Who?
I'm just a little thief digging graves
Meng Tinghui
As an official of the imperial court, you
How dare you use lynching? Is there any royal law left?
Do you know me now?
Talk to me about lynching and royal law
Are you worthy?
If it weren't for keeping your bitch's life
Track down the Huxiao Gang
I will cut you to pieces right now
Master Meng
Only if the evidence is conclusive can he be convicted again in accordance with the law.
Take it back to the Procuratorate
There are many instruments of torture there
Let's reminisce slowly
- take away - yes
Walk
Under the orders of Wan Shangshu of the Ministry of Punishment
Catch the thief who stole the body
Please also ask Mr. Meng to commit the crime
Leave it to our criminal department to deal with it
Your Ministry of Punishment will not care about it sooner or later.
My elders just arrested someone
You came just by smelling it
Jingzhao Mansion received a report
Has been transferred to the Ministry of Criminal Justice for investigation
What if I don't want to hand over the favor?
We were just ordered to pick someone up
If an adult blocks it
Don't blame us for being rude.
Captain Di
Obstructing the Criminal Department from handling the case
Chief current
I can capture you all together
superior
Master Meng
I really don’t want to confront my colleagues with swords.
If adults insist on obstructing law enforcement
Impeachment Memorial of Wan Shangshu
Will appear before the emperor tomorrow
Inspectorate of Justice
Has the right to perform directly
We might as well try
Impeachment memorials by the Procuratorate and the Ministry of Justice
Which one comes to the Holy Presence first?
The Ministry of Punishment is in charge of the world's criminal names
Even if the Holy Spirit comes in person
We also need to talk about the charter.
Today this prisoner
Our Ministry of Punishment is going to decide
Please also ask Mr. Meng to be aware of current affairs.
Otherwise, when Wan Shangshu comes in person,
You are not as easy to talk to as I am.
Master Meng
According to "Da Ning Law"
Involving major cases
or important suspect
Must be reported to the Ministry of Criminal Justice
Then leave it to the Holy Spirit to decide
This is the established procedure of the imperial court
Mr. Meng, please think again.
Master Meng
The Holy Father opened the Chawenyuan under pressure
Just established now
It is not appropriate to make enemies with the Ministry of Justice
My lord, we have just set up an ambush
People from the Criminal Department came here in the middle of the night
There must be some fraud in this matter
Why don't we take a long-term approach and catch the big fish?
I'll go to the Criminal Department and watch you
good
Today I will take a step back
But today's matter
I will report the truth to Your Majesty
Thank you, Mr. Meng, for your cooperation.
take people away
What's your expression?
Provoking my master
Master Meng
We have followed your instructions
The evil deeds of these evil people in the village
Write them down one by one
These are blood letters written anonymously by villagers
He also secretly stuffed it into me
In addition to digging graves and exhuming corpses, extorting money
They also dragged people to death with horses.
Crimes of the Tiger Roar Gang
It’s almost too many to write about
Before, some villagers reported to the official
It was also handled by the Ministry of Punishment.
But they were only detained for three days
Just let them all out
They are also becoming more arrogant
a fire
The villagers who burned the reporter to death
This time
I'm afraid we are also in trouble
Wan Kai, the Minister of Punishment, is from Zuo Xiangguo.
The Huxiao Gang can really come and go freely in the Criminal Department
This water is too deep
I will enter the palace right now to report to the Holy Emperor
Please Mr. Meng
You must save us
-Thank you, Mr. Meng. -Thank you, Mr. Meng.
-Get up quickly-Thank you, Mr. Meng
Get up first, get up
Yin Qing was summoned
Go to the Criminal Department first
Know the etiquette
You go mobilize the God Guards
I won't let him go this time
adult
They were really released
Master Meng
So generous
Come and pick us up in person
No need
we are in jail
Enough of good wine and good meat
If you think your life in the Ministry of Punishment is too comfortable,
Then go and try the prison food of my Chawenyuan
little girl
You really take yourself seriously
Do you still dare to report to the official?
At the feet of the emperor
How dare you regard the law as nothing?
stop
Stop it
No more suing
This little face is quite pretty
- Let go - What a pity
My heart is a bit poisonous
I spent three days in jail
Is it time to compensate me?
beast
Ah Cheng
We won't sue
No more suing
rise and rise
Ah Cheng
I didn’t see it clearly a few days ago
Look carefully today
This little face is quite pretty.
What a pity it is to be an official
Not as good as
Follow me, Second Master
Mr. Meng, you smell so good.
Ah Cheng
Lu Er
Today we will settle our old and new grudges together
Smelly bitches
Don't think that I won't dare to touch you once you become an official.
Kill them for me
- Let me see if any of you dare to move. - Stop.
Master Meng
Lu Er
Today I will make it impossible for you to survive
Can't die
The Divine Guards obey orders
take them down
yes
Meng Tinghui
How dare you touch a hair on my face today?
Our gang leader will definitely make your life worse than death in the future
I'm afraid he won't dare to come
I would like to take a look
Who is supporting you behind the scenes?
Let you be so unscrupulous
the person behind him
You can't afford it
Wait for him to punish you.
Today I will let you see clearly
How I use the Danin law to deal with sinners
execution
-well
Very good
Meng Tinghui
You stinky bitch
-well
A female official took up the case
Much better than those old men who can speak in official style.
I don’t know how many people these beasts have killed
I finally got my comeuppance today
Yes, kill him
- Beat him to death - Beat him to death
let him go
Give me a good look at it
How tragic will be Lu Er's fate?
Go back and tell your gang leader everything
I, Meng Tinghui, am waiting for him at the Procuratorate.
I'm in the Inspectorate for one day
The Tiger Roar Gang will definitely be uprooted
beat him to death
I will definitely bring the news to
stop
Meng Tinghui
A few little thieves
You are so inspiring
What do you want to do?
Keep playing
Bold
Meng Tinghui
How dare you do it in front of me?
Punish the people with a stick on the street
They are also considered common people
They are extremely vicious and deserve what they deserve
There is also the Tiger Roar Gang behind the scenes.
If I let them go today
-There will be endless troubles -Save me
You are the Minister of the Ministry of Justice
Indifferent to the grievances of the people
He also repeatedly stopped me from punishing evil and eradicating evil.
What are your intentions?
Master Meng
You are just a low-ranking official of the sixth rank
What a great official power
These people
Just stealing corpses and taking money
Why punish him on the street?
I must read this book for you today
If Wan Shangshu has a clear conscience, he can go
Meng Tinghui
Help him...
He will definitely avenge me
Come though
It's him I'm waiting for
Sir, he fainted
Well done Master Meng
-Yes, Lord Meng is Qingtian - Yin Qing
Drag the living ones behind the horses and bring them back
Meng Tinghui
Your methods are extremely cruel
I will enlighten you right away
-I will definitely take you... -As you wish
I'm just following my own rules
Treat the other person's body
Mom, try the breakfast at Fangzhuanlou
Freshly baked
You have a really good appetite
Meng Tinghui beat the body thief to death with a cane on the street
This incident has alarmed both the government and the public
As a minister of the Holy Emperor
Don’t want to take a look?
father
People depend on food
Only when you are full can you have the strength to work.
not to mention
Now the Holy Father is angry
I don't dare to mess with him
By the way, I heard them say
Now the memorial for the impeachment of Meng Tinghui by hundreds of officials
It's already piled higher than people.
They are all begging the Holy One to punish Meng Tinghui severely.
She got into such a big trouble this time
I don’t even know how angry the Holy Father will be.
The Procuratorate is already at the forefront of the storm
Meng Tinghui’s behavior
And different from the strict officials
Conflict is inevitable
The Inspection and Wen Yuan expected by the Holy One
What will happen in the future?
It just depends on the game between them.
You two, father and son
Are you really not worried at all?
Now this matter involves Zhili
She heard that Sheng Shang went to the Chawenyuan
I rushed over without even eating breakfast.
Ah Nian is too indulgent and polite.
This is midnight
They all went to the cemetery
I'm getting more and more courageous
Dad, don’t you think she is more rebellious than me?
-I am still good-A Nian still knows how to protect me
As your brother
Why don't you listen or ask?
I just know how to eat here
Obviously he knows etiquette and does not follow the rules
not me
never mind
Zhili has never experienced storms since childhood
Maybe you can go home after this incident
Then you don't know your sister very well.
Don't look at Zhili's gentle appearance
In fact, deep down
She is not confined to the boudoir
Not willing to accept the secular world, very stubborn
Look at A Nian
He moved into our home when he was ten years old
How mature and steady he is now
Not only do you think about me and your mother at all times,
I am more attentive to your sister
And you? Still eat
How come it's my fault again?
I can't afford to offend you, and I can't even afford to hide.
Let's go, mother
Don't waste
Let's go, dad
Rain is coming
Things are going to change
Sister Zhili
Ah Nian, why are you here?
I'm worried about you, not to mention
Executing the punishment of death with a stick
They are all the divine guards under my command.
The Holy Spirit summoned Mr. Meng alone
Idle people waiting
Do not disturb
Huang Yuwei
A stick of incense
I'm really worried about my adults
One died of serious injuries
Two people fainted on the spot
You caused this huge disaster
Meng Tinghui
Who gave you the courage?
have a look
within one day
This memorial is all for you
Why does the Holy One only listen to the one-sided words of the courtiers?
Don’t you go and see the grievances of the people?
Lu Er and those people
Previously coerced the governor of Jingzhao
Almost killed the general
Nowadays corpses are stolen for ransom
Even in front of the minister
Beat up Ah Cheng
Humiliating his wife in the street
Those beasts harmed the people and bullied women and children
Do all kinds of evil
Shouldn't he die?
Life and death have their own laws
The law is dead
But if those who enforce the law do not distinguish between good and evil, right and wrong,
The law is a piece of waste paper
Is it fair?
Meng Tinghui
Do you think you can kill a few of them?
Can you save the people from fire and water?
Do you know
Where is the lair of the Tiger Roar Gang?
Its influence penetrated into several places in the six departments of the imperial court
Who is the person behind it?
If we can't uproot them
Only more people will suffer
Saving hundreds of people is saving
Can you save someone?
Isn't it a rescue?
I am not as far-sighted as your Majesty.
I crawled out from among the dead
Long in the market
I’ve seen too many people’s lives become like nothing
The villain is now
Life and death are just a moment
If I hadn’t made a decisive decision yesterday,
Mr. and Mrs. Ah Cheng
At this moment, there are two corpses on the mass grave.
If the Holy Spirit saw it with his own eyes
Those wicked people buried the people in a pool of blood
Tear and insult
I will definitely not stand idly by
Don't you want to do it with your own hands?
Kill those evildoers who tortured the people with thousands of swords?
Do you dare to say that you have no selfish motives?
you abused your power
Do you think my trust is child's play?
You disappoint me so much
Your Majesty
Isn’t the purpose of the Procuratorate to punish rape and eliminate evil?
Why did the Holy Spirit stand for those executioners?
Seeking protection from the law?
The law is the law of the people
before becoming an official
They are also the people of Daning
The law should support the weak
But you shouldn’t save the lives of those who deserve to die
Could it be that the Chawenyuan is just the Holy One?
whitewash peace
Ornaments that display the image of the Holy King?
Our adults are crazy
It's totally treasonous
No one dares to be so disrespectful to the Holy One
You rely on my favor
Act wantonly
unrepentant
Then I want to ask you
What do you think of me and the Inspectorate?
your chess pieces
at your mercy
favor
between the minister and the sage
Isn't it a relationship of mutual use?
The Holy One is the one who holds the sword
But I can't find a sharp sword that I can use
Only then will they settle for the next best thing
Take a fancy to me
A dull knife that's not even a sword
If the Holy Spirit favors you
Let the wicked go free
Let the law become a joke
Let the people admit their grievances
Then this favor
I don’t care about it
Chen Ning makes a broken blade
But please have a clear conscience
A clear conscience?
Do you know that above this court?
He who has a clear conscience dies the fastest
Then Chen will be the first one
This is the position of chief of the Procuratorate
I am not worthy
I don’t dare to ask for it again
Your Majesty, although Mr. Meng has made mistakes,
But he also punished the villains who stole corpses
It made a name for the Inspectorate of Justice
Today there are already many people
Proactively present grievances
Removing Mr. Meng at this time
I'm afraid it's inappropriate
I haven't held you accountable yet
Instead, beg for mercy on her behalf.
She acts recklessly and impulsively
Shouldn't you be admonishing me?
I know the crime
Your Majesty
The Divine Guards failed to stop Master Meng in time
I have an unshirkable responsibility
Associate Shen cannot be blamed alone.
Your Majesty
Mr. Meng was speechless for a moment.
Not intending to offend His Majesty
I hope the Holy One will calm down.
What are you?
It's your place to interrupt here
It's really not a thing
He poisoned me as soon as he arrived
Yin Qing is my colleague in the Chawenyuan
Your Procuratorate is the place where you recruit white-faced men.
The Holy Spirit said this
It's a huge insult to me
Yin Qing is Bai Xiaosheng from Chawenyuan
He played a lot of role in catching the corpse thief.
The Holy One is dissatisfied with me
Just punish me alone
No need to vent your anger everywhere
from now on
Meng Tinghui moved out of here
adult
The Holy One is angry
Why don't you give in first?
Wait until the Holy One calms down
Make further plans?
Holy Oral Oral
Meng Tinghui acted impulsively and disrespected the Holy One
Immediately taken to the prison of the Ministry of Justice
wait and see
Although Mr. Meng made mistakes, he did it for the people.
I hope your Majesty will think twice.
The Holy Will has been made
We are just following orders
Please also ask Mr. Meng to cooperate.
Can…
Needless to say
I'll just go with you
The truth has been told before
It is difficult for women to take on big responsibilities
Take a look
Only a few days after taking office
That caused such trouble
The Holy Father always thinks that Zuo Xiangguo is meddling in other people's affairs.
But as soon as Xiangguo let go
Such a big mess happened
Or is it that Zuo Xiangguo has a sharp eye?
Our Kyoto style
When did a woman take charge?
Meng Tinghui is nothing to be afraid of
This woman is full of tricks
If you stay in Kyoto
Sooner or later it will be a disaster
take this opportunity
expel her from Kyoto
The further away from the Holy One, the better
Subordinates understand
Is it tasty?
Delicious, thank you brother
gang leader
Come on, Yangyang, Xiaobo
Take your brothers and sisters upstairs to eat
good
explain
Second child
dead
It’s Meng Tinghui from the Inspectorate of Justice
She asked me to tell the gang leader
Say don't hide like a turtle
she said
As long as she stays in the Procuratorate for one day
Tiger Roar Gang
There will be no peace
I hate mindless trash the most
Lu Er is dead
You should also go and accompany him.
No…
I have warned Lu Er a long time ago
Don't cause trouble during this time
The second child also messed up because of what happened last time.
Eager to make meritorious deeds
Then he stabbed Lou Zi again
I'll take some brothers with me
before dawn
Bring that bitch's head to see you
Are you going to die too?
gang leader
My second brother has been with you for so many years
Come in wind or rain
There is hard work even without credit.
If we just let Meng Tinghui go,
It's hard for him to close his eyes even under the Nine Springs.
Meng Tinghui dares to touch my people
Make her pay a hundred times the price
Thank you, helper
As long as I can avenge my second brother
Go up the mountain of knives and go down into the sea of ​​fire
No excuses
What can't you tell me in writing?
Do you have to meet?
The newly appointed Meng Tinghui
Killed my best friend
I will torture her to death with my own hands
The Holy Spirit established the Inspectorate
Specially designed to investigate the Huxiao Gang
Don’t you understand the seriousness of this matter?
He's just an insignificant subordinate.
Don't make a big deal out of it
negligible?
If I were ruthless
How could you be where you are today?
What are you afraid of?
She is just a woman
Abandoned by the Holy One
Now he is a prisoner again
If you don't care
I will go to the Ministry of Justice in person
stop
If something goes wrong between us
That is the great crime of killing the nine tribes
That's better
You and I, brothers, go on the road together
It’s good to have a companion on the road to Huangquan
residence
elder brother
you are too naive
From the first day you take this position
We are just people in the same boat
Do you want to get off the ship now?
late
I can give people to you
But you must act decisively
No one left alive
Then I will wait for the good news from my brother.
Miss Yan
small adult
I came here to find Assistant Manager Shen
It would be better if I met you
You have a close relationship with the Holy One
Can you please beg for mercy and let Meng Meng go?
I can't help you with this matter
Assistant Shen
Don't waste your efforts
I'm coming today
Just to take the gift back home
Tell her to stop interfering in this matter
You can just sit back and watch.
Why are you still trying to stop Assistant Manager Shen?
Meng Meng just killed a few people who deserved to die.
What was wrong with her?
What do you and Meng Tinghui think?
It’s really the same
No wonder we can be friends
The same goes for you and the Holy One.
ruthless
After a while, he was pampered and connected to the palace.
After a while, he turned ruthless and was thrown into jail.
So uncertain and moody
It's really chilling
Do you dare to speak arrogantly to His Majesty?
The Holy Spirit has his own considerations in mind
It's not your turn to point fingers.
It’s not my turn, what about you?
A dandy who relies on the favor of the Holy One
Who have you to yell at me?
Who is yelling?
You really know how to beat someone down
it's you
It's you who yelled at me
small adult
Why are you still arguing?
Who is this girl?
My name is Yan Fuzhi
You should be the Yin Qing Meng Meng often mentioned, right?
Where is Assistant Manager Shen?
Meng Meng was imprisoned
I want to ask her to help me enter the palace to see the Holy Emperor.
Pray for Meng Meng
Associate Shen prepared all night
Twenty Crimes of the Tiger Roar Gang
Presented to the Emperor
He also asked You Xiangguo to write a letter to help plead for mercy.
Your Majesty
- Didn't let go - Then I'll go by myself
I personally kowtow to the Holy One and admit my mistake.
I must see Meng Meng
Miss Yan
Wait for me for a while
good
Do you think the Holy One cares about your kowtow and admission of mistakes?
The Holy One cares about you. Go kowtow and admit your mistake.
Why should I kowtow and admit my mistake?
What does this have to do with me?
-You... -Stop arguing
The most important thing for us right now is to rescue Mr. Meng
Brother, you need someone to tie the bell to untie it.
We want to meet Lord Meng
This matter…
small adult
Meng Meng is now imprisoned in the prison of the Ministry of Punishment
I'm afraid they'll abuse lynching
I beg you
Help
let me go meet her
The Holy One has ordered
No one is allowed to visit
Meng Meng, you are so pitiful
He obviously made a contribution
Still have to be imprisoned in prison
Not enough to eat
Not warm enough to wear
Still have to be tortured
No one can help you
-Okay -What should I do?
alright
Don't cry
I'll make arrangements
real?